[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 31]
What is that?
I can't believe the Brahma Tree is glowing.
-Look. -This is...
My Lord's demon power.
What is My Lord
looking for?
It seems so messy.
He even used his spiritual power.
The Baffling Star Stone.
This medicine
may help Liu Shao.
Liu Shao.
You've come to the right person.
[The Six-star Brilliant Array]
Come on.
Show me your precious ancient book.
The Six-star Brilliant Array
will not be available until the eclipse.
It's not hard.
The eclipse is in three days.
It's perfect.
Really?
But this array
seals the divine spirit,
which is more difficult than the Demon King sealing the Immortal Ze Shui.
And we need the help of the masters of three palaces.
It's not easy.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to
my senior sister and the old Immortal Master.
Besides,
the eclipse is still a few days away.
I don't want him to feel bad.
If you would
tell Luo Ge about this,
it would be much less trouble.
No.
I have to
deal with this on my own.
He
probably wants your powers to stop working against each other.
Senior sister,
the Immortal Master agreed.
Please help Liu Shao.
I can
help her.
But,
it's just...
If Luo Ge picks on you,
what are you gonna do?
There's something wrong when you put it that way.
Maybe Luo Ge already knew.
He already knew?
What would you do
if you got the wrong idea?
When you put it that way,
things are a little tricky.
But when Luo Ge came out of the Yin-yang Cave,
he told us to find a way
to nourish Liu Shao's body.
I think he already knew
and wanted to be prepared.
Really?
Liu Shao.
Are you really ready
for the seal tomorrow?
Shang Yurong helped me get the Immortal Master
and Master Zhuo to help.
It shouldn't go wrong.
Okay.
Then I'll eat the melon
and cheer for you.
But I still can't rest easy.
I still feel like something is gonna happen.
Is there something
the God of the Sun wants to tell me?
It has been bothering me.
The God of the Sun
doesn't want me to seal it?
I don't think you've figured it out yet.
Sun Spirit
is not a good thing at all.
Let's not talk about that.
When your seal is done,
you and my brother are no longer at odds.
And then you can be together.
Even if Luo Ge knows,
he would be happy.
How did the Bone Melting Pool suddenly so much evil spirits?
Go and ask the Immortal Master.
Master Zhuo.
What happened?
General Xie said he's going to worship his junior sister today.
Soon after he left,
the evil spirits inside suddenly began to change.
So we reported it to the Immortal Mater.
We wanted other generals to help us.
I didn't realize it was you.
You guys wait here.
I'll go inside.
Yes.
Zhuo Qiuxian.
Oh, no.
Master Zhuo.
Who's running wild here?
How presumptuous!
Master Zhuo,
you are on a roll now.
You've forgotten
your master's last words, right?
It has nothing to do with my master.
Am I wrong?
If Lord Shang saw his only son
had always been a general for a thousand years,
would he be disappointed?
Nonsense!
By then,
will you still have the momentum?
Get lost!
What's going on?
Why am I having these hallucinations?
There's something wrong with the Bone Melting Pool.
You need to be on your guard at all times.
If anything goes wrong,
report it immediately.
-Yes. -Yes.
Liu Shao.
Don't worry.
I have your Tears of the Half-Demon.
Yes.
You can do it.
The sealing process
of the Sun Spirit
is extremely dangerous.
If you regret it now,
it's not too late.
Liu Shao.
You need to think this through.
After all,
the seal of the divine spirit is never done before.
I'm very clear.
For the Three Realms,
and for Luo Ge,
this is my decision.
They are
sealing the divine spirit.
The divine spirit is resisting the formation.
Go on.
Change!
You are on a roll now.
You've forgotten
your master's last words, right?
You're not gonna get away with this!
The weapon of the God of the Sun,
Crown Wheel.
I can't believe you summoned the Crown Wheel.
You're sure you're up against me,
not the one under the Four Seasons Monument?
Why did the Crown Wheel attack Qiuxian?
Looks like Zhuo Qiuxian
has been affected by the evil spirit.
Luo Ge!
I can't keep it up!
Help me!
Shang Yurong.
Get your senior sister settled
and meet me at the Palace Chonghua.
Luo Ge.
Was the seal successful?
Liu Shao.
Is it
worth it?
As long as you no longer suffer because of me,
as long as our spiritual powers no longer collide,
I think it's worth it.
Sun Spirit was your chance
to advance your mana.
I don't expect anything from that.
You know me, don't you?
All I want is to be with you.
It would certainly be best
if we were together.
But we not only have each other,
but also the whole Three Realms.
But you're all I got.
I know you're responsible for the Three Realms.
I can't affect you.
Isn't this the best of both worlds?
I just don't think it's worth it.
Actually,
you should understand.
But I think it's worth it.
Speaking of the Three Realms,
how about I take you to the mortal world to have a look?
You could see
how precious
your Sun Spirit is.
Okay.
Senior.
You're awake.
Rong.
What happened?
Well, well...
There was a problem sealing Liu Shao's divine spirit.
You're not gonna get away with this!
I almost ruined the formation
and killed Liu Wei?
No, no.
Liu Shao's fine.
She has Luo Ge watching over her.
How could it go wrong?
Wasn't that an accident?
If Luo Ge hadn't showed up in time,
Liu Shao might have...
What happened to me that day?
Senior.
Don't worry.
I've asked.
When you were in the Bone Melting Pool,
you were accidentally affected by the evil spirits.
So...
So you got caught up in the moment.
What?
Impossible.
My mind is complete.
How could I get caught up?
I know.
Don't be nervous.
Let me get you a cup of tea.
Shang Yurong hasn't become an immortal yet,
which embarrassed the Lord Shang.
Luo Ge kept him down very badly.
Where would he get a promotion?
You can't affect my Rong.
Senior!
How can there be
such strong evil spirits in the Bone Melting Pool?
Your senior has recovered.
Senior.
The evil spirit that affected Master Zhuo's mind
should have come from the Four Seasons Monument.
Someone had broken through Master Zhuo's defense
and confused her mind
under the cover of the Bone Melting Pool's evil spirits.
But,
my senior has been diligent in her practice.
How can she be confused by the evil spirit?
The evil spirit
comes from personal attachment.
Your senior had a lot on her shoulders
and ended up in the grip of obsession.
It's natural that
she did something wrong.
I'm the reason
she's like this.
Shang Yurong.
At this time,
I feel as if the evil spirit has been awakened.
But
it was meant to weaken me.
I'm taking Liu Shao away for a few days.
I need your help,
so I can walk away.
I'm going there
to find a suitable solution
to the evil spirit
for the current situation.
Maybe
I can get an unexpected boost.
You're thinking about Shao again?
Look at you.
What do you have to worry about
when Shao's in Immortal Palace?
Shao is lucky
to go to the Immortal Palace.
No one else could ask for that.
Oh,
my little girl.
How nice to have you by my side.
Dad!
I'm back!
Dad! Mom!
Shao!
My little Shao!
Is this our Shao?
Shao.
Our Shao has made it big
and became a fairy now.
I came back to see you today.
And I brought...
Luo Ge.
I need you to meet my parents.
Okay.
Lu Li!
No!
He is the immortal of Immortal Palace.
Hello, Immortal.
Thank you
for taking care of Shao.
My daughter is very promising.
She's not only an immortal disciple who guards the mortal world,
but also led the Immortal home.
Do you know?
This is the place when I first
met an Immortal when I was a child.
So,
this is where you started,
changing your destiny
and becoming the guardian of the Three Realms?
What you just said,
the Immortal told me exactly the same.
Wang Jian
made a special appointment with us today.
Liu Shao!
Immortal Luo Ge.
Since my brother came back,
I've been remembering
to send someone here to clean up.
-Cheers! -Cheers!
You're the only one taking the credit.
You don't have to remember.
Someone will clean it up.
Brother, sister-in-law.
You have no idea.
Since you went back to Immortal Palace,
this place has become a shrine.
People come here every day to pray for good luck.
What did you two do?
Nothing.
I just spread the story of
how the Immortal Luo Ge restored the boundary of the Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
put down Ao Yin,
and restored peace to the world.
Every festival,
people specifically came here.
to pray for heaven lanterns.
They are very religious.
Tell me.
The mortal world
has everything in the Immortal Palace.
But what is found in the mortal world
may not be found in the Immortal Palace.
Why
does everyone want to be a fairy?
Look.
The beauty of the mortal world
is protected by someone.
In order to protect these beauties,
there's Immortal Palace.
and people like Marquis Wuyang
striving to be an immortal.
Looking at the hard life of mortals,
people like us should be more diligent.
You possess the Sun Spirit,
which is enough to show that
you are the chosen one.
Don't let personal feelings
hinder your progress.
Yes.
Destiny?
What are you talking about?
Luo Ge took Liu Shao to mortal world.
again?
Yes.
Master Shang is in charge of
the affairs of the Immortal Palace for the time being.
Nonsense!
You can go first.
Yes.
Luo Ge! Luo Ge!
Are you crazy?
You just left the Immortal Palace like this?
Do you still want to be a god?
No.
I can't let him ruin his future like that.
Wouldn't that be better?
Luo Ge is in love.
That's your chance.
Who?
Who are you?
Who am I?
I am you.
Have you forgotten
what you did?
No.
I didn't do that!
No!
Luo Ge.
You want to protect the Three Realms?
Guess
what gifts
and surprises
I have in store for you?
What people want
is just water
and food.
If there's no one to protect the world,
the evil will prevail.
Then the world is like the Avici Hell.
A great ship can carry a heavy load. A steed can travel a long way.
You have inherited Sun Spirit,
so you have a responsibility in this world.
I understand what you're trying to say.
But, Luo Ge, do you know?
It wasn't my intention
to get Sun Spirit.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm a shadow.
I have to live someone else's life.
I've searched for the Baffling Star Stone from He Na.
It should help you improve quickly.
My Lord.
What do you want to ask?
Just say it.
Don't hesitate.
The Baffling Star Stone
was supposed to boost the vitality.
And Miss Liu Shao was trying to seal the divine spirit.
Well, I don't think it's a good fit for her.
Why did you...
Liu Shao and Luo Ge.
They've done so much
for the peace of the Three Realms.
I'm just
making a small contribution to the demon world.
I understand.
My head is spinning.
What's wrong with me?
You're sick
because you just sealed the divine spirit.
The Master is refining the Star Stone.
During this time,
you need to work hard on the Crown Wheel.
But you also need to pay attention to the method.
If your spirit vein is damaged,
the consequences may be catastrophic.
What do you think?
Good.
I didn't expect
you could make rapid progress
after you sealed the divine spirit.
I think
it's the Crown Wheel that's helping me.
After all, it's Sun's weapon.
I could feel a power
return to my body.
If I practice enough,
I'll get familiar with the power of the Crown Wheel.
If anything happens to the Four Seasons Monument,
I can help you.
Looks like
after all these days,
you finally figured it out.
Liu Shao.
You always
amaze me.
I want to defend the Three Realms
with you.
The most important thing is that you are also the person I want to protect.
They must have had a good time on earth.
And I'm still waiting to ask my brother about the curse.
I wonder when they'll be back.
Immortal, you're back.
Brother.
Did you
have a good time on earth these days?
Tell me about it.
I made this tea with freshly picked dew.
Try it.
It's good.
I'm sure
that's not why you came to me.
Tell me.
What is it?
I think,
the years of separation
between the demon world
and the Immortal Palace
are the years of punishment for the whole race.
That should be enough.
This curse was put by the god.
No one could break it.
But the god is merciful.
Even if it's a curse,
there should be some leeway.
You came to talk to me
for Fu?
Now the Four Seasons Monument
is not impregnable.
Liu Shao has been working on the Crown Wheel for the Four Seasons Monument.
But all you do is think about that Fu.
He is not a good man.
Stay away from him.
Brother!
I don't think so!
You can't say that about him!
He is not a good guy,
but he's not a bad guy.
Get back in there right now.
Grounded.
Brother!
Immortal Luo Ge.
Master Shang is waiting for you at the Litian Temple.
Brother!
Hello?
Well done.
As long as Luo Ge returns to the Immortal Palace,
he can only keep wasting his immortal energy.
Every time he is weak,
I'm stronger.
As long as Luo Ge keeps doing this,
the Three Realms will be mine sooner or later.
I have practiced for ten thousand years.
How could I be affected by the evil spirit?
How could it be me?
Immortal Master, there are cracks in the Four Seasons Monument.
Master Shang asked you to go to the Litian Temple.
They didn't find anything, did they?
The new cracks are different from the past.
They're destroyed by external forces.
He could enter the Four Seasons Monument boundary
and destroy the Four Seasons Monument.
It must be someone inside the Immortal Palace.
The disciples who died at the Four Seasons Monument
should also be killed by this man.
Besides,
the Bone Melting Pool connects the Life Gate at the bottom of the Four Seasons Monument.
There're constantly evil spirits gushing out.
You are right.
I always suspected
there was a traitor in the Immortal Palace.
He is very cunning.
Although I eliminated the evil spirits of the Yin-yang cave
and the Four Seasons Monument is temporarily stable,
the Four Seasons Monument is not as good as before
after thousands of years.
I'm actually worried that
if we don't get rid of the inside man,
one day the Four Seasons Monument will collapse.
The one under the Four Seasons Monument
has always been looking for an opportunity.
He wanted to send the evil spirits into the Bone Melting Pool,
where they would take root.
The power of the God of Moonlight was so great,
but his mind was also destroyed by the evil spirit.
If they accumulate too much in the Bone Melting Pool,
no one in the Immortal Palace
can bear it.
I'll remove the evil spirits from the Bone Melting Pool
myself.
But you need to watch out the disciples for being invaded by the evil spirits.
Don't
give that guy under the Four Seasons Monument a chance.
We need to get rid of that evil
before we can rest easy.
Xie Lingqi.
We meet again.
Immortal,
you
condensed so much evil spirits
into a bead?
There should be no evil spirit left.
Otherwise, the Bone Melting Pool
still has the chance to become a gathering place of evil spirits.
But Immortal, you already have an injury.
And you used the Spring to repair the Four Seasons Monument again.
How do you hold up on your own?
This is what he wanted.
You mean he did it
to wear out your aura?
Immortal!
Luo Ge!
The Immortal used too much spiritual power.
It may have injured his inner organs and spirit vein.
I'll take him out for medical treatment.
Then I'll stay here.
I'll keep an eye on the monster under the Four Seasons Monument.
As for the inside man,
if I find him,
I will catch him.
Okay. Thank you, General Xie.
Bad brother! Bad brother!
All you do is lock me up.
This boundary...
Oh, no.
I broke my brother's boundary.
How... How is that possible?
Oh, my god.
Don't worry.
I've just had a lot of things going on lately.
I just overdid it.
I'll be fine
if I rest for a while.
Immortal,
you've just recovered from this.
When will your body recover
after you've done such a big thing since you came back?
Listen.
Don't do this all the time.
I can't bear it.
Your body
will not be able to withstand this ordeal.
It's nothing serious.
Anyway, Luo Ge is an Immortal.
Master,
come on.
If you can't talk,
don't talk.
He's right.
That vicious creature did this on purpose.
It looks like
it's going to do something soon.
Luo Ning.
Didn't your brother ground you?
How did you get out?
I was just gonna ask you about that.
Is there something wrong with my brother?
Today,
I just used a little more strength.
I can't believe I broke
my brother's boundary.
Your brother's boundary
for his family is pretty arbitrary.
Besides, it has something to do with his own condition.
It took him a lot of effort
to seal the evil spirits today.
So you got a good deal.
I'm glad he's fine.
Then I won't visit him,
lest he lock me up again.
If he tries to lock you up next time,
tell him I'm looking for you.
You can hide in my place.
You are the best.
By the way, Immortal Master,
there's something
I want to ask you about.
What is it?
It has something to do with what happened in the aquatic demon world.
I wonder
what's going on
with the aquatic demon curse.
Okay.
It's just as well that you know.
Back then,
Immortal Ze Shui
learned that the man who would marry her
was not the lake fairy,
but the Demon King.
She wanted to run away right then and there.
But
her immortal energy was imprisoned.
So she was forced to stay in the demon world.
I don't know how long it took.
One day,
she broke the seal with the magic weapon
and came to the Brahma tree.
Tree Fairy,
you always thought
we really loved each other.
But now?
Is this what happens
when you really love each other?
What he did
was no different from a monster.
The paths of the fairy and the demon are really different.
Turns out
what the old immortals said
was right.